http://www.football-results.org/council/privacy.html

.
Privacy
Copyright (c) 2005-2020 Wycombe and South Bucks Minor Football League
Sponsored by Enterprise Trophies and Engraving
WSBMFL Privacy Policy
The Wycombe & South Bucks Minor Football League takes your privacy very seriously. This Privacy Notice sets out how we use and look after the personal information we collect from you. We are the data controller, responsible for the processing of any personal data you give us. We take reasonable care to keep your information secure and to prevent any unauthorised access to or use of it.
What personal data we hold on you and other officers within your club
Personal data means any information about an individual from which that individual can be identified. We collect, use, store and transfer some personal data of the key officers within your Club as well as Team Officials. When you register with the League whether by filling in forms at an event or online, or by corresponding with us by phone, e-mail or otherwise you provide information to us about your Club Officers and Team Officials only with their express permission. The information you give us may include your/their name, address, e-mail address, phone number(s) and gender. Where we hold this data from you, it will be agreed that your club has explicit consent from the individuals.
Why we need such personal data
We will only use personal data for the legitimate purpose(s) for which it has been specifically provided. The reason we need participants personal data is to be able to run an efficient league. Processing activites include arranging matches, notifying match/contact information with your opponents/referee(s)/league committee members and we do this by publishing personal data in the League Directory where it is shared with other member Clubs via the League Website portal. The shared personal details are name, email address and phone/mobile number but not postal address. As a Club Official/ Committee member your contact detail is shared with all clubs and team officials in the League. As a Team Manager or Team Fixture Official your shared contact details are visible only to :-
· Resticted Team Officials (i.e. only those Team Officials in the same age group and only if their club has affiliated them)
· Club Officials - typically committee members of Clubs that have affiliated to the League.
· Committee members of the League
We respect our user's privacy and will not pass Club Officers and Officials personal details to anyone else outside of the above categories.
You can see the data the League holds about your role at your club, as provided by one of your club officials to us, by signing in to the portal on the League website and clicking on the 'Profile' option from the top of the screen. To start using the Portal, please read this privacy policy and register for an account. By signing in to the League website, you are confirming you have read and accepted these privacy policy terms.
We also use personal data, password and a cookie to authenticate helpers nominated by the member Club so they may sign in and rate the opposition team for Fairplay / Respect behavior. We keep rating scores and associated comments to manage behavior and discipline within the League. We aggregate scores together with submissions made by other teams over a long period of time in order to produce Fairplay Tables which are published.
We do not share individual submissions made about other teams.
Other parties we share your personal data with
To play in the League, Player name dat of birth and identity information will have been entered onto the FA Whole Game System database, which is administered by the FA and shared with the League. As an officer of your Club, you are required to gain explicit consent from your player's parent or guardian before providing this data to us via the FA Whole Game.
We may use this information on rare occaisions pass it to the County FA.
The League Directory and the Fairplay administation is accessed vie the League website where it is processed by Thinkable Cloud Ltd under contract to the League.
The League website also collects anonymous aggregated information including busy days and times, browser and screen capability, number of hits, impressions, visitors to the site and other similar information. Google Analytics is used to better understand how site visitors navigate to and through our site, how long is spent visiting our content items and how often they return to visit our Site. It is used by the Processor to prioritise development and for other site maintenance purposes. The aggregate number of visitors is periodically published on this site to help third parties determine the value of advertising on it. It is not possible to identify individual users from this data and no private or personally identifiable information is passed to advertisers or third parties.
Protection of your personal data
We have put in place appropriate security measures to prevent your personal data from being accidentally lost, used or accessed in an unauthorised way, altered or disclosed.
How long we hold your personal data
We keep personal data on our participants and members while they continue to be a participant or member (in most cases for a 5 year period) or are otherwise actively involved with the League. We delete personal data from the League Directory and Fairplay system
during the season after a participant or member has left or otherwise ended their membership or affiliation. Sometimes it is deleted sooner if specifically requested and we are able to do so. We may need to retain some personal data for longer for legal or regulatory purposes.
Third Party Sites
This policy covers information collected through this web site. Participating football clubs will have their own policies. This website privacy policy does not cover our member clubs or other manual methods.
The personal data that is stored on Whole Game System is subject to the FA privacy policy so we advise you review that policy together with this League notice. If you would like your personal data to be deleted from Whole Game System then please contact the FA.
Terms of use of this website:
You agree to not create a false identity or forged e-mail address or header, or otherwise attempt to mislead others as to the identity of the sender or the origin of the message
You agree to not attempt to gain unauthorized access to the League Directory, or Fairplay service, other accounts, computer systems or networks connected to the Service, through password mining or any other means
You agree to not interfere with another members use and enjoyment of the Service or another entitys use and enjoyment of similar services							You agree to not send us or other members unlawful, abusive, threatening, or otherwise objectionable material of any kind or nature
You agree to not transmit any material that may infringe the intellectual property rights or other rights of third parties, including trademark, copyright or right of publicity
You agree to not use the update service in connection with chain letters, junk e-mail, spamming or any duplicative or unsolicited messages for your employer or club, commercial or otherwise
You agree to not harvest or otherwise collect information about other members, including e-mail addresses, without their consent
You may not supply, sell or license content from the Fixtures or Fairplay database, or a copy of it, to any other person or company or organisation
